I need to make sure the radio is off. Because I cannot hear anything and the display shows the current time 9:50 p.m. the radio is off.
Now I will press and hold the first alarm button until the display flashes.
now I will press the hour button. I can see the hour is increasing. current time is in p.m., because PM light on the left side is on.
I will keep pressing the button until the p.m. light is on and the number is 8.
Now I will press the minute button to increase the minute.
Because I want to set the alarm at 8 o'clock so I keep increasing the minute until I see the time is 8 o'clock.
Now the time changes back to the current time. What I need to do next is to set ringtone as buzzer.
Now it uses the radio as the ringtone, because now the display shows a green dot on the music icon.
Now I need to change the ringtone.
I wll press and hold the first alarm button until the display flashes. Then I will press the alarm button until the green light besides the alarm symbol is on.
Now The ringtone is set.
So, the task is now.